<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dynamics on Atcults - sculpting online presense</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/tags/dynamics/</link><description>Recent content in dynamics on Atcults - sculpting online presense</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:39:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/tags/dynamics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamics 365 Plans and Pricing</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Dynamics-365-Plans-and-Pricing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:39:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Dynamics-365-Plans-and-Pricing/</guid><description>Microsoft sells Dynamics 365 in 4 different plans:
• Dynamics 365 plan
• Customer Engagement Plan
• Unified Operation Plan
• Separate Applications
Customer Engagement Plan:
This plan includes apps that are useful for Customer Relationship Management (CRM), such as Sales, Customer Service, Project Service Automation, and Field Service.
The new Dynamics 365 for Marketing has some limitations:
• If the Customer Engagement plan purchased has 10 or more users the Marketing app is included with no additional charges for 2,000 contacts.</description></item><item><title>What Is Dynamics 365</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/What-Is-Dynamics-365/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:39:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/What-Is-Dynamics-365/</guid><description>Microsoft has announced the upcoming availability of “Dynamics 365”. Set to be released this fall, Dynamics 365 promises to “turn business process into business advantage for organizations everywhere”.
Dynamics is a combination of CRM and ERP:
Dynamics 365 is a cloud-based ERP and CRM enterprise system. It was built by Microsoft for maximum flexibility and extensibility.
Microsoft already has significant plays in ERP and CRM. Dynamics 365 is the next step in the evolution of a combined ERP and CRM product.</description></item><item><title>What Is Sales Processing in Microsoft Dynamics 365</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/What-Is-Sales-Processing-in-Microsoft-Dynamics-365/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:01:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/What-Is-Sales-Processing-in-Microsoft-Dynamics-365/</guid><description>Introduction:
This blog explains the whole sales process from Lead to Invoice.
Sales Procedure:
• This process begins with the Lead creation and ends with Invoice.
Step – 1: Lead:
• Go to Sales -&amp;gt; Leads.
• This will redirect to the following page:
• It will show the default view of the Leads.
• Click New and provide the details.
• Click Save.
• Click Qualify.
Step – 2: Opportunity:</description></item></channel></rss>