<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>digital on Atcults - sculpting online presense</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/tags/digital/</link><description>Recent content in digital on Atcults - sculpting online presense</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 15:22:45 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/tags/digital/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Secret Unveil How Social Media Marketing Can Help You Take Your Business to the Next Level</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Secret-Unveil-How-Social-Media-Marketing-Can-Help-You-Take-Your-Business-to-the-Next-Level/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 15:22:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Secret-Unveil-How-Social-Media-Marketing-Can-Help-You-Take-Your-Business-to-the-Next-Level/</guid><description>It can be said that the common buzzword for marketers these days is “social media marketing”. These marketers normally aim to optimise their online strategy and the conversion rate. It is rapidly becoming the most featured part of successful internet marketing strategies.
"Owing to the advantages of social media marketing and the businesses across the world are discovering methodologies through which this media can lead to success and assist them to grow their online business.</description></item><item><title>3 Key Elements of Success of Digital Marketing Campaigns</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/3-Key-Elements-of-Success-of-Digital-Marketing-Campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:41:52 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/3-Key-Elements-of-Success-of-Digital-Marketing-Campaigns/</guid><description>Digital marketing is a phenomenon if practiced correctly, then it gives amazing results and returns. Unlike traditional marketing, the digital marketing gives wider exposure, highly controlled environment and tractability to the marketing campaigns. This helps in gaining a lot of benefits such as, increased business, well defined strategies and measurement of each metric to devise a fine tuned digital marketing strategy for future campaigns.
"The digital marketing campaigns are made up of various factors and elements and in this article we will talk about the top 3 most crucial elements of success in the digital realm.</description></item><item><title>Four Key Elements of Digital Presence and Their Necessity</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Four-Key-Elements-of-Digital-Presence-and-Their-Necessity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:41:23 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Four-Key-Elements-of-Digital-Presence-and-Their-Necessity/</guid><description>Today’s consumers and businesses are digitized. They start their research online and end up buying online. Thus, a strong digital presence of a business is inevitable for any small, medium and large scaled businesses. To create a strong digital presence the businesses often take help of digital marketing experts. The digital marketing experts run various online marketing campaigns and the business leverages certain business benefits and online exposure. Is this it?</description></item><item><title>Top 3 SEO Tips for an ECommerce Website</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Top-3-SEO-Tips-for-an-ECommerce-Website/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:40:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Top-3-SEO-Tips-for-an-ECommerce-Website/</guid><description>The advent of the internet has made it easier for entrepreneurs to run a company with ease. It also led to the situation where the digital market is teeming with competitors who are doing everything they can to capture maximum market share in minimal time delay.
"To ensure that your e-commerce site is making money in the long run, you should make sure that you are doing all that you can to ensure it is getting the exposure it needs to thrive!</description></item><item><title>Why Culture Is More Important in Digital Marketing</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Why-Culture-Is-More-Important-in-Digital-Marketing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:40:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Why-Culture-Is-More-Important-in-Digital-Marketing/</guid><description>Digital Marketing is not a tactic, it is an art amalgamated with a strategic approach. An effective digital marketing strategy considers the many facets before actually getting executed such as, demography, budget, buyers’ persona, expected results, etc. There is one more hidden gem that must be kept in mind by the digital marketing experts yet it is often overlooked. I am talking about the culture and cultural values of your target audience.</description></item><item><title>Why It Is Must to Make Sure Your Website Design Is Unique!?</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Why-It-Is-Must-to-Make-Sure-Your-Website-Design-Is-Unique!?/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:39:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/Why-It-Is-Must-to-Make-Sure-Your-Website-Design-Is-Unique!?/</guid><description>For any business, whether small or large, the uniqueness of the content on its web page is the most important criteria which are mandatory and needs to be fulfilled at any cost! It is so because there are several other business sectors which are probably selling similar items or services at a fixed cost. To attract the right consumers, companies have to show their individual approach which is exclusive and unique!</description></item></channel></rss>