<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on Atcults - sculpting online presense</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on Atcults - sculpting online presense</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 15:58:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Microsoft Dynamics 365</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/microsoft-dynamics-365/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 15:58:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/microsoft-dynamics-365/</guid><description>If you’re ready to learn how Dynamics 365 can help your business, you’re in the right place. Simply know how you can grow, evolve and transform every part of your business to better meet the needs of your customers. We’ll show you how you can capture new opportunities across your business when you bring people, data, and processes together with Microsoft business solutions -intelligent cloud applications that unify CRM and ERP capabilities to help you run your business end to end.</description></item><item><title>Power Bi</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/power-bi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/power-bi/</guid><description>Power BI is a business analytics service that delivers insights to enable fast, informed decisions. Transform data into stunning visuals and share them with colleagues on any device. Visually explore and analyze data—on-premises and in the cloud—all in one view. Collaborate on and share customized dashboards and interactive reports. Scale across your organization with built-in governance and security.</description></item><item><title>Mobile and Web Apps</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/mobile-and-web-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 15:57:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/mobile-and-web-apps/</guid><description>WEB DEVELOPMENT
A company’s website is the front door to its brand. The design, content and navigability of your website all send a message. AMF Media Group develops a deep understanding of your audience and combines that with your company’s online vision. We integrate audio, video, still images, animation, text and data for the delivery of interactive content, all in a search-engine friendly design. Then we keep the site fresh and brand focused.</description></item><item><title>Digital Marketing</title><link>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 15:30:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://ranjeetbarsa.github.io/services/digital-marketing/</guid><description>Digital marketing is the promotion of products or brands via one or more forms of electronic media. Digital marketing is often referred to as online marketing, internet marketing or web marketing. Digital marketing has been around for quite some time but it hasn’t been very well defined. We tend to think that digital marketing encompasses banner advertising, search engine optimization (SEO) and pay per click. Yet, this is too narrow a definition, because digital marketing also includes e-mail, RSS, voice broadcast, fax broadcast, blogging, podcasting, video streams, wireless text messaging, and instant messaging.</description></item></channel></rss>